1. openBrowser(URL)
5. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Home Page/header_digibox"))
9. click(findTestObject("Registration/icon-acount"))
13. custom.BrowserHelper.closeFirefoxPopup()
17. setText(findTestObject("Registration/field-account"), "agungpriyadi")
21. setText(findTestObject("Registration/field-Password"), "Laskar123456")
25. click(findTestObject("Login/btn-sign in"))
29. click(findTestObject("Registration/icon-acount"))
33. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Home Page/verify-succes-acount-login"))
37. click(findTestObject("Home Page/Search/icon-search"))
41. click(findTestObject("Home Page/Search/field-search"))
45. sendKeys(findTestObject("Home Page/Search/field-search"), Keys.chord("IPHONE 12 PRO MAX 128GB GOLD", ENTER))
49. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Home Page/Search/verify-product-iphone-12 -pro"))
53. click(findTestObject("Product and Cart/Add to cart/btn-product - IPHONE 12 PRO MAX 128GB GOLD"))
57. click(findTestObject("Product and Cart/Add to cart/button_Add to Cart"))
61. waitForElementPresent(findTestObject("Product and Cart/Add to cart/i_icon-cart"), 7)
65. click(findTestObject("Product and Cart/Add to cart/i_icon-cart"))
69. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Ship To/btn_checkout"), STOP_ON_FAILURE)
73. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Ship To/btn_checkout"))
77. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Order Summary/Online Payment - Cradit Card"))
81. check(findTestObject("Checkout/Order Summary/Checkbox__I accept"))